(Raj:)Congratulations.
Does it have that new-car smell?
(Howard:)Yep. For as long
as I can keep my mother out of it.
If you wanna check it out later,
it's parked right out front, Space 294.
- I'm sorry, 294?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)That's my parking spot.
(Raj:)Why do you have a parking spot?
You don't have a car. You don't drive.
(Sheldon:)It doesn't matter. That's my spot.
(Leonard:)Maybe they reassigned it
because you never use it.
(Sheldon:)I'm not using my nipples either.
Maybe they should reassign those.
(Howard:)Sheldon, someday, if you get a car...
(Howard:)...I'm sure they'll give you
another parking space.
(Sheldon:)I don't want another parking space.
I want my parking space.
Well, it's perfect. It's a corner spot,
cutting the risk of door dings in half.
(Sheldon:)It's a mere 28 steps
from the building entrance.
(Sheldon:)The nearby tree provides shade
on hot days...
(Sheldon:)...and is also home
to a delightful squirrel...
(Sheldon:)...which is fortuitous
because most squirrels are real jerks.
(Howard:)Fun story.
Meanwhile, you still don't have a car.
(Sheldon:)Don't try to change the subject.
(Sheldon:)This is about a parking space.
It has nothing to do with cars.
(Howard:)Are you listening to yourself?
(Sheldon:)I always listen to myself.
It's one of the great joys of my life.
(Sheldon:)- Now get your car out of my spot.
- Nope.
(Sheldon:)Very well, you leave me no choice.
(Sheldon:)What are you looking at,
you stupid squirrel?